Sing-along Subtitles By:
MightyMike77020
She isn't coming yet, Toto.
Did she hurt you?
She tried to, didn't she?
Come on. We'll go tell
Uncle Henry and Auntie Em.
Come on, Toto.
Aunt Em! Aunt Em!
Aunt Em, just listen to what
Miss Gulch did to Toto!
Dorothy, please! We're
trying to count!
Oh, but Aunt Em, she hit him over the...
Don't bother us now, honey.
This old incubator's gone bad
and we're likely to lose
a lot of our chicks.
Oh... oh, the poor
little things.
Oh, but Aunt Em,
Miss Gulch hit Toto right over the
back with a rake just because
she says he gets in her garden and
chases her nasty old cat every day!
Seventy. Dorothy, please!
Oh, but he doesn't do it every
day, just once or twice a week.
And he can't catch
her old cat anyway.
And now she says she's gonna
get the sheriff, and,...
Dorothy! Dorothy! We're busy!
All right.
How's she coming?
Take it easy.
Ow!
You got my finger!
Why don't you get your
finger out of the way?
There you are.
Right on my finger!
It's a lucky thing
it wasn't your head.
Zeke, what am I going
to do about Miss Gulch?
Just because Toto
chases her old cat.
Listen, honey, I got
them hogs to get in.
Now lookit, Dorothy, you ain't
using your head about Miss Gulch.
Think you didn't have
any brains at all.
I have so got brains!
Well why don't you use them?
When you come home, don't
go by Miss Gulch's place.
Then Toto won't get in her garden, and
you won't get in no trouble. See?
Oh, Hunk, you just won't
listen, that's all.
Well, your head ain't
made of straw, you know.
Ow!
Sooey!
Get in there before I make
a dime bank out of ya!
Listen, kid.
Are you going to let that old
Gulch heifer try and buffalo ya'?
She ain't nothing to be afraid of.
Have a little courage, that's all.
I'm not afraid of her.
Then the next time she squawks, walk
right up to her and spit in her eye.
That's what I'd do!
Oh!
Zeke!
Zeke! Help me please! Get
me out of here! Help!
Oh!
Are you all right, Dorothy?
Yes, I'm all right.
Oh!
I fell in and Zeke.
Why, Zeke, you're just
as scared as I am!
What's the matter?
You gonna let a little old pig
make a coward out of ya'?
Look at you, Zeke
your justa' bunch of...
Here, here. What's all this jabber-wapping
when there's work to be done?
I know three shiftless farm hands that'll
be out of a job before they know it!
Well, Dorothy was
walking along the...
I saw you tinkering with
that contraption, Hickory.
Now, you and Hunk get
back to that wagon!
All right, Mrs. Gale.
But some day they're going to erect
a statue to me in this town, and,...
Well, don't start
posing for it now.
Here, here, can't work on an empty stomach.
Have some crullers.
- Gosh, Mrs. Gale.
- Oh, thanks.
- Just fried.
- Swell.
You see, Dorothy toppled
in with the big Duroc...
It's no place for Dorothy
about a pig sty!
Now, you go feed those hogs before
they worry themselves into anemia!
Yes'am.
Auntie Em, really, you know what
Miss Gulch said she was gonna do to Toto?
She said she was gonna,...
Now, Dorothy, dear,
stop imagining things.
You always get yourself
into a fret over nothing.
Now, you just help us out today
and find yourself a place where
you won't get into any trouble.
Some place where there
isn't any trouble.
Do you suppose there
is such a place, Toto?
There must be.
It's not a place you can get
to by a boat or a train.
It's far, far away.
Behind the moon.
Beyond the rain.
♪ Somewhere, over the rainbow, ♪
♪ way up high. ♪
♪ There's a land that I heard of ♪
♪ once in a lullaby. ♪
♪ Somewhere, over the rainbow, ♪
♪ skies are blue, ♪
♪ and the dreams that you dare
to dream, really do come true. ♪
♪ Someday I'll wish upon a star ♪
♪ and wake up where the
clouds are far behind me. ♪
♪ Where troubles melt like lemon drops, ♪
♪ away above the chimney tops, ♪
♪ that's where you'll find me. ♪
♪ Somewhere, over the rainbow, ♪
♪ bluebirds fly. ♪
♪ Birds fly over the rainbow, ♪
♪ why then, oh, why can't I? ♪
♪ If happy little bluebirds fly ♪
♪ beyond the rainbow, ♪
♪ why, oh, why can't I? ♪
Mr. Gale.
Howdy, Miss Gulch.
I want to see you and your
wife right away about Dorothy.
Dorothy? Well, what has Dorothy done?
What's she done? I'm all but
lame from the bite on my leg!
You mean, she bit you?
No, her dog!
Oh, she bit her dog, eh?
No!
That dog's a menace
to the community.
I'm taking him to the sheriff
and make sure he's destroyed.
Destroyed? Toto?
Oh, you can't! You mustn't!
Auntie Em!
Uncle Henry! You
won't let her, will you?
Of course, we won't.
Ah, will we, Em?
Please, Aunt Em!
Toto didn't mean to.
He didn't know he was doing anything wrong.
I'm the one that ought to be punished.
I let him go in her garden. You can
send me to bed without supper.
If you don't hand over that dog, I'll bring
a damage suit that'll take your whole farm!
There's a law protecting
folks against dogs that bite!
How would it be if she keeps him tied up?
He's really gentle, with
gentle people, that is.
Well, that's for the sheriff to decide.
Here's his order allowing me to take him.
Unless you want to
go against the law.
Uhh,...
Yeah.
Now, we can't go against the law, Dorothy.
I'm afraid poor Toto will have to go.
Now you're seeing reason.
Here's what I'm taking him in,
so he can't attack me again.
Oh, no, no! I won't let you take him!
You go away, you...! Oooh,
I'll bite you myself!
Dorothy!
You wicked old witch!
Uncle Henry, Auntie Em,
don't let 'em take Toto!
- Don't let her take him, please! Stop her!
- Here! I've got an order! Let me have...
- Put him in the basket, Henry.
- The idea!
Don't, Uncle Henry.
Oh, Toto!
Toto!
Almira Gulch, just because
you own half the county
doesn't mean you have the
power to run the rest of us!
For 23 years I've been dying to
tell you what I thought of you!
And now...
Well, being a christian
woman, I can't say it!
Toto, darling! Oh,
I've got you back!
You came back!
Oh, I'm so glad!
Toto!
Oh, they'll be coming
back for you in a minute.
We've got to get away!
We've got to run away!
Well, well, well!
Houseguests, huh?
And who might you be?
No, no, now don't tell me.
Let's see. You're...
You're traveling in disguise.
No, that's not right.
I, you're.
You're going on a visit.
No, I'm wrong.
That's... you're...
You're running away.
How did you guess?
Professor Marvel never guesses.
He knows!
Now why are you running away?
No, no, now don't tell me.
They, they don't understand you at home.
They don't appreciate you.
You want to see other lands, big
cities, big mountains, big oceans.
Why, it's just like you could
read what was inside of me.
Yes,
Toto, that's not polite!
We haven't been asked yet.
He's perfectly welcome.
As one dog to another, huh?
Now, let's see. Where were we?
Oh, please, Professor,
why can't we go with you
and see all the crowned
heads of Europe?
Do you know any? You
mean, the... thing.
Yes eh, well eh, I eh,...
I never do anything without
consulting my crystal first.
Let's eh, go inside here, we'll eh,
just come along. I'll show you.
That's right. Here, sit right down here.
That's it.
This, this is the same genuine,
magic, authentic crystal
used by the priests of Isis and Osiris
in the days of the pharaohs of Egypt,
in which Cleopatra first saw the approach
of Julius Caesar and Marc Anthony, and eh,
and so on and so on.
Now eh, you eh, you'd better close
your eyes, my child,
for a moment, in order to be
better in tune with the infinite.
We eh, we can't do these things without
reaching out into the infinite.
Yes. That's, that's all right. Now you
can open them. We'll gaze into the crystal.
Ahh.
What's this I see?
A house with a picket fence
and a barn with a weather vane and a...
Of a, of a running horse.
That's our farm!
Yes, yes, there's, there's
a woman, she's...
She's wearing a polka-dot dress.
Her face is careworn.
That's Aunt Em.
Yes. Her eh, her name is Emily.
That's right. What's she doing?
Well, I, I can't quite see.
Why, she's crying!
Someone has hurt her. Someone has
just about broken her heart.
Me?
Well, it's eh, someone
she loves very much.
Someone she's been very kind to, someone
she's taken care of in sickness.
I had the measles once and she
stayed right by me every minute.
Uh-huh.
What's she doing now?
Well, she's eh...
What's this?
Why, she's, she's putting
her hand on her heart,
she's, she's dropping down on the bed!
Oh, no, no!
Well, that's all, the
crystal's gone dark.
Oh, you, you don't suppose she
could really be sick, do you?
Oh, oh, I've got to go home right away!
But, what's this? I thought
you were going along with me.
Oh, no, no, I have to get to
her right away! Come on, Toto!
Come on! Come on!
Goodbye, Professor Marvel,
and thanks a lot!
Better get under cover, Sylvester,
there's a storm blowing up, a whopper,
to speak in the vernacular
of the peasantry.
Poor little kid. I hope
she gets home all right.
Hunk, get them horses loose!
Where’s Hickory.
Hickory! Hickory!
Doggone it Hick!
it's a twister! It's a twister!
Dorothy!
Come on, everybody
in the storm cellar!
Henry! Henry! I can't find Dorothy!
She’s somewhere out in the storm!
Dorothy!
We can't look for her now!
Come on get in the cellar. Hurry up!
Auntie Em!
Auntie Em! Uncle Henry!
Oh!
Cluck-cluck-cluck-cluck.
Cluck-cluck-cluck.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Moo.
Ruff! Ruff!
Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!
We must be up
inside the cyclone!
Oh! Miss Gulch!
Aaaahh!
Aahh!
Ahh!
Oh!
Toto, I've a feeling we're
not in Kansas anymore..
We must be over the rainbow!
Now I, I know we're not in Kansas.
Are you a good witch
or a bad witch?
Who, me?
I'm not a witch at all. I'm
Dorothy Gale from Kansas.
Oh!
Well, is that the witch?
Who, Toto?
Toto's my dog.
Well, I'm a little muddled.
The Munchkins called me because a new
witch has just dropped a house
on The Wicked Witch of the East. And
there's the house, and here you are
and that's all that's left
of the Wicked Witch of the East.
And so what the Munchkins want to know is,
are you a good witch or a bad witch?
But, I've already told you,
I'm not a witch at all,
witches are old and ugly.
What was that?
The Munchkins. They're
laughing because I am a witch.
I'm Glinda, the Witch of the North.
You are?
Oh, I beg your pardon!
But I've never heard
of a beautiful witch before.
Only bad witches are ugly.
The Munchkins are happy because
you have freed them from the
Wicked Witch of the East.
Oh, but if you please, what are Munchkins?
The little people who live in this land.
It's Munchkinland
and you are their national
heroine, my dear.
It's all right, you may
all come out and thank her.
♪ Come out, come out
wherever you are. ♪
♪ And meet the young lady
who fell from a star. ♪
♪ She fell from the sky,
she fell very far. ♪
♪ And Kansas, she says, is
the name of the star. ♪
♫ Kansas, she says,
is the name of the star. ♫
♪ She brings you good news,
or haven't you heard? ♪
♪ When she fell out of Kansas
a miracle occurred. ♪
♪ It really was no miracle
what happened was just this: ♪
♪ the wind began to switch,
the house to pitch. ♪
♪ The wind began to switch,
♪ And suddenly the hinges
started to unhitch. ♪
♪ Just then the witch,
to satisfy an itch. ♪
♪ Went flying on her broomstick
thumbing for a hitch. ♪
♪ And, oh, what happened then was rich. ♪
♫ The house began to pitch,
the kitchen took a slitch. ♫
♫ It landed on the Wicked Witch
in the middle of a ditch. ♫
♫ which was not a healthy
situation for the Wicked Witch. ♫
♫ The house began to pitch,
the kitchen took a slitch. ♫
♫ It landed on the Wicked Witch
in the middle of a ditch. ♫
♫ which was not a healthy
situation for the Wicked Witch. ♫
♫ Who began to twitch,
and was reduced to just a stitch. ♫
♫ Of what was once the Wicked Witch. ♫
We thank you very sweetly.
For doing it so neatly.
You've killed her so completely.
That we thank you very sweetly.
Let the joyous news be spread.
The wicked old witch at last is dead!
♫ Ding-dong the witch is dead!
Which old witch? ♫
♫ The Wicked Witch. Ding-dong
the Wicked Witch is dead. ♫
♫ Wake up, you sleepyhead. Rub
your eyes, get out of bed. ♫
♫ Wake up, the Wicked Witch is dead. ♫
♫ She's gone where the goblins
go below, below, below. ♫
♫ Yo-ho, let's open up and sing
and ring the bells out. ♫
♫ Ding-dong the merry-oh,
sing it high, sing it low. ♫
♫ Let them know the Wicked Witch is dead. ♫
As Mayor of the Munchkin city.
In the county of the land of Oz
I welcome you most regally.
But we've got to verify it legally.
- To see.
- To see?
- To see
- if she.
- If she?
- if she
is morally, ethically.
Spiritually, physically.
Positively, absolutely.
Undeniably and reliably dead.
♪ As coroner I must aver ♪
♪ I thoroughly examined her. ♪
♪ And she's not only merely dead. ♪
♪ She's really most sincerely dead. ♪
Then this is a day of independence
for all the Munchkins
and their descendants.
If any.
Yes, let the joyous news be spread.
The wicked old witch at last is dead!
Yay!
♫ Ding-dong the witch is dead! Which
old witch? The Wicked Witch! ♫
♫ Ding-dong the Wicked
Witch is dead. ♫
♫ Wake up, you sleepyhead. Rub
your eyes, get out of bed. ♫
♫ Wake up, you MightyMike77020. Rub
♫ Wake up, you sleepyhead. Rub
your eyes, get out of bed. ♫
♫ Wake up, the Wicked
Witch is dead. ♫
♫ She's gone where the goblins
go below, below, below. ♫
♫ Yo-ho, let's open up and sing
and ring the bells out. ♫
♫ Ding-dong the merry-oh,
sing it high, sing it low. ♫
♫ Let them know the Wicked
Witch is dead! ♫
♫ We represent The Lullaby League. ♫
♫ The Lullaby League, The Lullaby League. ♫
♫ and in the name of The Lullaby League. ♫
♫ We wish to welcome you
to Munchkin land. ♫
♫ We represent The Lollypop Guild. ♫
♫ The Lollypop Guild, The Lollypop Guild. ♫
♫ and in the name of The Lollypop Guild. ♫
♫ We wish to welcome you
to Munchkin land. ♫
♫ We welcome you to Munchkin land. ♫
♫ Tra la la la la la ♫
♫ Tra la la Tra la la ♫
♫ Tra la la la la la la ♫
From now on you'll be history.
You'll be hist... You'll be hist...
You'll be history
♪ and we will glorify your name. ♫
♫ and we will glorify your name. ♫
♪ You'll be a bust. ♪
- ♪ Be a bust ♪
- ♪ be a bust. ♪
♫ In the hall of fame ♫
♫ in the hall of fame ♫
♫ Tra la la la la Tra la la Tra la la ♫
♫ Tra la la la la la la. ♫
♫ Tra la la la la la. ♫
Ahhh!
Ahh!
I thought you said she was dead.
That was her sister,
the Wicked Witch of the East.
This is The Wicked Witch of the West.
She's worse than the other one was.
Who killed my sister? Who
killed The Witch of the East?
Was it you?
No, no. It was an accident. I
didn't mean to kill anybody.
Well, my little pretty, I
can cause accidents, too!
Aren't you forgetting
The Ruby Slippers?
The Slippers, yes!
The Slippers!
They're gone!
The Ruby Slippers! What
have you done with them?
Give them back to me or I'll.
It's too late! There they are
and there they'll stay!
Give me back my slippers!
I'm the only one who
knows how to use them.
They're of no use to you.
Give them back to me.
Give them back!
Keep tight inside of them.
Their magic must be very powerful,
or she wouldn't want them so badly.
You stay out of this, Glenda,
or I'll fix you as well!
Rubbish! You have no power here.
Begone, before somebody
drops a house on you, too!
Very well, I'll bide my time.
And as for you, my fine lady,
it's true I can't attend to
you here and now as I'd like
but just try to
stay out of my way.
Just try!
I'll get you, my pretty,
and your little dog, too!
It's all right. You can get up.
She's gone.
It's all right. You
can all get up.
What a smell of sulphur!
I'm afraid you’ve made rather a bad
enemy of The Wicked Witch of the West.
The sooner you get out of Oz altogether,
the safer you'll sleep, my dear.
I'd give anything to get
out of Oz altogether, but
which is the way back to Kansas?
I can't go the way I came.
No, that's true. The only
person who might know
would be the great and wonderful
Wizard of Oz himself!
The Wizard of Oz? Is he
good or is he wicked?
Oh, very good, but very mysterious.
He lives in The Emerald City,
and that's a long journey from here. Did
you bring your broomstick with you?
No, I'm afraid I didn't.
Well, then, you'll have to walk.
The Munchkins will see you safely
to the border of Munchkinland.
And remember, never let those Ruby
Slippers off your feet for a moment
or you will be at the mercy of
The Wicked Witch of the West.
But, how do I start for Emerald City?
It's always best to
start at the beginning
and all you do is follow
The Yellow Brick Road.
But, what happens if I...
Just follow The Yellow Brick Road.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Goodbye....
My!
People come and go
so quickly here!
Follow The Yellow Brick Road.
Follow The Yellow Brick Road?
♫ Follow The Yellow Brick Road. ♫
♫ Follow, follow, follow, follow,
follow The Yellow Brick Road. ♫
♫ Follow The Yellow Brick,
follow The Yellow Brick ♫
♫ Follow The Yellow Brick Road. ♫
♫ You're off to see The Wizard ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz ♫
♫ you'll find he is a whiz of a Wiz
if ever a Wiz there was. ♫
♫ if ever oh ever a Wiz there was the
Wizard of Oz is one because ♫
♫ because, because, because,
because, because... ♫
♫ because of the wonderful things he does ♫
♫ You're off to see The Wizard. ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz! ♫
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Bye....
Follow The Yellow Brick Road?
Follow The Yellow...
Now which way do we go?
Pardon me. That way
is a very nice way.
Who said that?
Arf! Arf-Arf! Ruff!
Arf! Arf! Arf! Arf!
Arf!
Don't be silly, Toto.
Scarecrows don't talk.
It's pleasant down
that way, too.
That's funny.
Wasn't he pointing
the other way?
Of course, people
do go both ways.
Why, you did say
something, didn't you?
Are you doing that on purpose,
or can't you make up your mind?
That's the trouble. I
can't make up my mind.
I haven't got a brain,
only straw.
How can you talk if you
haven't got a brain?
I don't know.
But some people without brains do an
awful lot of talking, don't they?
Yes, I guess you're right.
Well, we haven't really
met properly, have we?
Why, no.
How do you do?
Very well, thank you.
Oh, I'm not feeling at all well.
You see, it's very tedious
being stuck up here
all day long with a pole
up your back.
Oh, dear, that must be terribly
uncomfortable. Can't you get down?
Down? No, you see, I'm, well, I'm,...
Oh, well, here, let me help you.
Oh, that's very kind of you, very kind.
Well, oh, dear, I don't
quite see how I can,
Of course, I'm not bright
about doing things
but if you'll just
bend the nail down
in the back, maybe
I'll slip off and come...
Oh, yes.
Ohhhh, woops.
There goes some of me again!
Ohh! Does it hurt you?
Oh, no. I just keep picking it
up and putting it back in again.
My! It's good to be free!
Oh! Oh! Ohhh!
Did I scare you?
No, no, I, I just thought
you hurt yourself.
But I didn't scare ya'?
No, of course not.
I didn't think so.
Caw
caw
Boo!
Caw
Scat!
Boo!
Caw
You see, I can't
even scare a crow.
They come from miles around just to
eat in my field and-and laugh in my face.
Oh, I'm a failure,
because I haven't got a brain.
Well, what would you do
with a brain if you had one?
Do? Why, if I had a brain, I could,
♪ I could wile away the hours, ♪
♪ conferrin' with the flowers. ♪
♪ Consultin' with the rain. ♪
♪ And my head I'd be scratchin' ♪
♪ while my thoughts were busy hatchin' ♪
♪ if I only had a brain. ♪
♪ I'd unravel every riddle
for any individ'le ♪
♪ in trouble or in pain. ♪
♪ With the thoughts you'll be thinkin' ♪
♪ you could be another Lincoln. ♪
♪ If you only had a brain. ♪
♪ Oh, I would tell you why ♪
♪ the ocean's near the shore. ♪
♪ I could think of things
I never thunk before, ♪
♪ and then I'd sit and think some more. ♪
♪ I would not be just a nuffin' ♪
♪ my head all full of stuffin' ♪
♪ my heart all full of pain ♪
♪ I would dance and be merry, ♪
♪ life would be a Ding-a-derry ♪
♪ if I only had a brain. ♪
Whoa!
Wonderful!
Why, if our scarecrow back in Kansas could
do that, the crows'd be scared to pieces!
- They would?
- Um-hmm..
Where's Kansas?
That's where I live.
And I want to get back there so badly
I'm going all the way to Emerald City
to get The Wizard of Oz to help me.
- You're going to see a Wizard?
- Um-hmm.
Do you think if I went with you this
Wizard would give me some brains?
I couldn't say.
But even if he didn't, you'd be
no worse off than you are now.
Yes, that's true.
But maybe you'd better not.
I've got a witch mad at me,
and you might
get into trouble.
Witch?
Huh! I'm not afraid of a witch!
I'm not afraid of anything!
Except a lighted match.
I don't blame you for that.
But I'd face a whole box full of them
for the chance of getting some brains.
Look,
I won't be any trouble
because I don't eat a thing.
I won't try to manage things
because I can't think.
Won't you take me with you?
Why, of course I will!
Hooray! We're off to see a Wizard!
Oh, well, you're not
starting out very well.
Oh, I'll try! Really, I will.
- To Oz?
- To Oz!
♪ We're off to see The Wizard ♪
♪ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz ♪
♪ we hear he is a whiz
of a Wiz ♪
♪ if ever a Wiz there was ♪
♪ if ever oh ever
a Wiz there was, ♪
♪ The Wizard of Oz
is one because ♪
♪ Because, because, because,
because, because. ♪
♪ Because of the wonderful
things he does. ♪
♪ We're off to see The Wizard ♪
♪ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz! ♪
Oh!
Apples!
Oh, look!
Oh!
Ouch!
What do you think you're doing?
We've been walking a long
ways and I was hungry and...
Did you say something?
- She was hungry!
Well, how would you like to have someone
come along and pick something off of you?
Oh, dear! I keep forgetting
I'm not in Kansas.
Come along, Dorothy, you don't
want any of those apples. Hmm!
Are you hinting my apples
aren't what they ought to be?
Oh, no! It's just that she doesn't
like little green worms!
Oh you...!
Ahhh!
You can't do that to me!
I'll show you how to get apples.
Oh.
Hooray! I guess that did it! Help yourself.
Why, it's a man!
A man made out of tin!
- What?
- Yes.
Oh!
Look!
Oil can!
Did you say something?
He said, "Oil can."
Oil can what?
Oil can?
Oh, here it is!
Help!
Where do you want to be oiled first?
My mouth! My mouth!
He said his mouth.
The other side....
Mm.....Mm... My... my,
my goodness, I can talk again!
Oh, oil my arms,
please, oil my elbows.
Here.
Oh...
Oh, did that hurt?
No, it feels wonderful.
I've held that axe up for ages.
Oh, goodness!
How did you ever get like his?
Oh, well,...
about a year ago, I was chopping that tree,
when suddenly it began to rain
and right in the middle of
a chop, I,... I rusted solid.
I've been that way ever since.
Well, you're perfect now.
My neck. My... My neck.
Perfect?
Bang on my chest if you
think I'm perfect.
Go ahead, bang on it.
Beautiful! What an echo!
It's empty.
The tinsmith forgot to give me a heart.
No heart?
No heart.
All hollow.
Oh!
♪ When a man's an empty kettle. ♪
♪ He should be on his mettle. ♪
♪ And yet I'm torn apart. ♪
♪ Just because I'm presumin' ♪
♪ that I could be kind-a human, ♪
♪ if I only had a heart ♪
♪ I'd be tender, I'd be gentle. ♪
♪ And awful sentimental. ♪
♪ Regarding love and art ♪
♪ I'd be friends with the sparrows. ♪
♪ And the boy who shoots the arrows. ♪
♪ If I only had a heart. ♪
♪ Picture me, a balcony ♪
♪ above a voice sings low ♪
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
♪ Lub dub I hear a beat... Lub dub ♪
♪ How sweet! ♪
♪ Just to register emotion, ♪
♪ jealousy, devotion. ♪
♪ And really feel the part ♪
♪ I could stay young and chipper. ♪
♪ And I'd lock it with a zipper. ♪
♪ If I only had a heart. ♪
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Are you all right?
I'm afraid I'm a little rusty yet.
Oh, dear!
That was wonderful!
You know.
We were just wondering why you couldn't
come with us to The Emerald City
ask The Wizard of Oz for a heart.
Well, suppose The Wizard wouldn't
get me one when we got there?
Oh, but he will!
He must!
We've come such
a long way already.
You call that long?
Why, you've just begun!
Helping the little lady along,
are you, my fine gentlemen?
Well, stay away from her
or I'll stuff a
mattress with you!
And you!
I'll use you for a beehive!
Here, Scarecrow!
Want to play ball?
Help, help! Fire!
I'm burning!
I'm not afraid of her.
I'll see you get safely
to The Wizard now
whether I get a brain or not!
"Stuff a mattress with me," hah!
I'll see you reach The Wizard,
whether I get a heart or not.
"Beehive," bah!
Let her try and make
a beehive out of me!
Oh...
You're the best friends
anybody ever had.
And it's funny, but I feel as
if I've known you all the time.
But I couldn't have, could I?
I don't see how.
You weren't around when I was stuffed
and sewn together. Were you?
And I was standing over there
rusting for the longest time.
Still, I wish I could remember. But
I guess it doesn't matter anyway.
We know each other
now, don't we?
- That's right.
- We do.
- To Oz?
- To Oz!
♫ We're off to see The Wizard ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz. ♫
♫ We hear he is a whiz of a Wiz ♫
♫ if ever a Wiz there was. ♫
♫ If ever a Wiz there was. ♫
♫ If ever, oh ever, a Wiz there was ♫
♫ The Wizard of Oz is one because. ♫
♫ Because, because, because,
because, because. ♫
♫ Because of the wonderful
things he does. ♫
♫ We're off to see The Wizard ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz. ♫
I don't like this forest!
It's...
It's dark and creepy!
Of course, I don't know, but I think
it'll get darker before it gets lighter.
Do...
Do you suppose we'll meet any wild animals?
We might.
Oh,...
Animals that, that eat straw?
Some, but mostly lions,
and tigers, and bears.
Lions?
And tigers?
And bears.
Oh!
Lions and tigers and bears!
Oh, my!
Roar!
Oh, look!
Ralf.
Rrralf.
Grrr.
Ralf.
Rrralf.
Huh.
Put 'em up! Put 'em up!
Which one of you first?
I'll fight you both
together, if you want.
I'll fight you with one
paw tied behind my back!
I'll fight you
standing on one foot!
I'll fight you with
my eyes closed.
Oh...
Pulling an axe on me, eh?
Sneaking up on me, eh?
Why...
Ruff!
Here, here. Go 'way
and let us alone!
Oh, scared, huh?
Afraid, huh?
How long can you stay
fresh in that can?
Come on, get up and fight,
you shivering junkyard! Hiss.
Put your hands up, you
lopsided bag of hay!
Now that's getting personal, Lion.
Yes, get up and
teach him a lesson.
Well, what's wrong
with you teaching him?
Well, well, well, I hardly know him.
Arf!
Arf! Arf!
Arf! Arf! Arf!
Well I'll get you anyway, pee-wee.
Rrralf.
No! Toto!
Shame on you!
What, what did you do that for?
I didn't bite him.
No, but you tried to.
It's bad enough picking
on a straw man,
but when you go around picking
on poor little dogs,...
Well, you didn't have
to go and hit me, did ya'?
Is my nose bleeding?
Well, of course not.
My goodness, what a
fuss you're making!
Well, naturally, when you go around picking
on things weaker than you are,
why, you're nothing
but a great big coward!
You're right, I am a coward!
I haven't any courage at all.
I even scare myself.
Look at the circles
under my eyes.
I haven't slept in weeks.
Why don't you try
counting sheep?
That doesn't do any good.
I'm afraid of them.
Aw, that's too bad.
Don't you think The Wizard
could help him, too?
I don't see why not.
Why don't you come
along with us?
We're on our way to see The Wizard now.
To get him a heart.
And him a brain.
I'm sure he could give
you some courage.
Well...
Wouldn't you feel degraded to be
seenin the company of a cowardly lion?
I would.
No, of course not!
Gee, that's, that's awfully nice of ya'.
My life has been
simply unbearable.
Oh...
Well, it's all right now. The
Wizard'll fix everything.
It's, it's been in me so long
I just... gotta tell
you how I feel.
Well, come on!
♪ Yeh, it's sad, believe me, Missy ♪
♪ when you're born to be a sissy, ♪
♪ without the vim and verve. ♪
♪ But I could show my prowess, ♪
♪ be a lion not a mou-ess, ♪
♪ if I only had the nerve. ♪
♪ I'm afraid there's no denyin' ♪
♪ I'm just a dande-lion, ♪
♪ a fate I don't deserve. ♪
♪ I'd be brave as a blizzard, ♪
♪ I'd be gentle as a lizard ♪
♪ I'd be clever as a gizzard. ♪
♪ If The Wizard is a Wizard
who will serve. ♪
♪ Then I'm sure to get a brain. ♪
♪ A heart. A home. The nerve. ♪
♫ Oh, we're off to see The Wizard ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz. ♫
♫ We hear he is a whiz of a Wiz ♫
♫ if ever a Wiz there was ♫
♫ if ever, oh ever, a Wiz there was ♫
♫ The Wizard of Oz is one because ♫
♫ because, because,
because, because, because ♫
♫ because of the wonderful
things he does! ♫
♫ We're off to see The Wizard ♫
♫ The Wonderful Wizard of Oz! ♫
A-hah!
So, you won't take warning, eh?
All the worse for you!
I'll take care of you
now instead of later!
Hah!
When I gain those Ruby Slippers, my
power will be the greatest in Oz!
And now, my beauties
something with poison
in it, I think.
With poison in it
but attractive to the eye
and soothing to the smell.
Poppies.
Poppies will put them to sleep.
Sleep.
Now they'll sleep.
There's Emerald City!
Oh, we're almost there at last! At last!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Just like I knew it would be.
He really must be a wonderful
wizard to live in a city like that!
Well, come on, then.
What are we waiting for?
Nothing! Let's hurry!
Yes, let's run!
Yes.
Come on, come on!
Hurry! Hurry!
Oh look!
Come on!
Look, you can see it here.
It's wonderful!
Emerald City!
Oh...
What's happening?
What is it?
I can't run anymore.
I'm so sleepy.
Here, give us your hands,
and we'll pull you along.
Oh, no, please.
I have to rest for just a minute.
Toto!
Where's Toto?
Oh, you rest now.
We're nearly there.
Don't cry, you'll rust yourself again!
Comin' to think of it,
forty winks wouldn't be bad.
Don't you start it, too!
Oh! We ought to try
and carry Dorothy.
I don't think I could,
but we could try.
- Let's.
- Yes.
Oh, now look at him!
This is terrible!
Here, Tin Man, help me.
Oh!
Oh, this is terrible,
can't budge her an inch!
This is a spell, this is!
It's the Wicked Witch!
What'll we do?
Help!
It's no use screaming
at a time like this!
Nobody will hear you!
Help!
Help, help!
It's snowing!
No, it isn't!
Yes, it is!
Maybe that'll help!
Oh, but it couldn't help.
It does help. Dorothy,
you're waking up!
Oh...
Oh!
Ah...
Unusual weather we're
having, ain't it?
Look, he's rusted again!
- Oh, give me the oil can, quick! Oh-oh,
- Here! Oil him.
- He is rusted.
- Here.
Here.
Quick, oh!
Oh!
Curses! Curses! Somebody
always helps that girl!
But shoes or no shoes, I'm still
great enough to conquer her.
And woe to those who
try to stop me!
Come on, let's get out of here.
Look, Emerald City is closer
and prettier than ever!
♫ You're out of the woods you're
out of the dark you're out of the night. ♫
♫ Step into the sun
step into the light. ♫
Step into the light. ♫
♫ Step into the sun
step into the light. ♫
♫ keep straight ahead
for the most glorious place, ♫
♫ on the face of the earth
or the sky. ♫
♫ Hold onto your breath hold
onto your heart hold onto your hope. ♫
♫ march up to the gate
and bid it open. ♫
Haaa!
To The Emerald City
as fast as lightning!
♫ You're out of the woods
you're out of the dark. ♫
♫ You're out of the night. ♫
♫ Step into the sun, step into the light. ♫
♫ march up to the gate and bid it open. ♫
♫ Open. ♫
Who rang that bell?
We did!
Can't you read?
Read what?
The notice!
What notice?
It's on the door, as plain
as the nose on my face!
It, ah. Oh...
Oh...
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
"Bell out of order,
please knock."
Well, that's more like it.
Now, state your business!
We want to see The Wizard.
Ooh!
The Wizard?!?
But nobody can see The Great Oz!
Nobody's ever seen The Great Oz!
Even I've never seen him!
Well, then, how do you
know there is one?
Because he,... I,... oh!
You're wasting my time!
Oh, please! Please sir...
I've got to see The Wizard.
The Good Witch of
the North sent me.
Prove it!
She's wearing the Ruby
Slippers she gave her!
Oh... so she is!
Well, bust my buttons!
Why didn't you say that
in the first place?
That's a horse
of a different color!
Come on in!
Cabby! Cabby! Just what
you're looking for!
Take you any place in
the city, we does!
Would you take us
to see The Wizard?
The Wizard? The Wizard?
I, can't,...
Well... yes, of course.
But first I'll take you to a little
place where you can tidy up a bit wot?
Oh, thank you so much.
We've been gone such a
long time, and we feel so mess...
What kind of a horse is that?
I've never seen a horse
like that before!
No, and never
will again, I fancy.
There's only one of him,
and he's it.
He's the horse of a different
color you've heard tell about.
♪ Ha, ha, ha ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho. ♪
♪ And a couple of tra, la, las. ♪
♫ Tra, la, las. ♫
♪ that's how we laugh the day away ♪
♫ that's how we laugh the day away ♫
♪ in the merry old land of Oz. ♪
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ Bzz, bzz, bzz ♪
♫ Bzz, bzz, bzz ♫
♪ Chirp, chirp, chirp. ♪
♫ Chirp, chirp, chirp. ♫
♪ and a couple of la-di-das. ♪
♫ and a couple of la-di-das. ♫
♪ that's how the crickets crick all day ♪
♫ that's how the crickets crick all day ♫
♪ in the merry old land of Oz. ♪
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ We get up at 12:00 ♪
♫ We get up at 12:00 ♫
♪ and start to work at 1:00. ♪
♫ and start to work at 1:00. ♫
♪ take an hour for lunch ♪
♫ take an hour for lunch ♫
♪ and then at 2:00 we're done. ♪
♫ and then at 2:00 we're done. ♫
♪ Jolly good fun! ♪
♫ Jolly good fun. ♫
♪ Ha, ha, ha ♪
♫ Ha, ha, ha ♫
♪ Ho, ho, ho. ♪
♫ Ho, ho, ho. ♫
♪ and a couple of tra-la-las. ♪
♫ and a couple of tra-la-las. ♫
♪ that's how we laugh the day away ♪
♫ that's how we laugh the day away ♫
♪ in the merry old land of Oz. ♪
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ Ha, ha, ha ♪
♫ Ha, ha, ha ♫
♪ Ho, ho, ho. ♪
♫ Ho, ho, ho. ♫
♫ and a couple of tra-la-las. ♫
♪ Ho, ho, ho. ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha. ♪
♫ and a couple of tra-la-las. ♫
♪ that's how we laugh the day away. ♪
♫ that's how we laugh the day away. ♫
♪ with a ho, ho, ho ♪
♫ with a ho, ho, ho ♫
♪ Ha, ha, ha. ♪
♫ Ha, ha, ha. ♫
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ Pat, pat here, ♪
♪ Pat, pat there ♪
♪ and a couple of brand new straws. ♪
♫ that's how we keep you young and fair ♫
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ Rub, rub here, ♪
♪ Rub, rub there ♪
♪ Whether you're tin or brass. ♪
♫ that's how we keep you in repair ♫
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♪ We can make a dimpled
smile out of a frown. ♪
♪ Can you even dye my eyes
to match my gown? ♪
♪ Uh-huh. ♪
♪ Jolly old town! ♪
♪ Clip, clip here, ♪
♪ Clip, clip there ♪
♪ We give the roughest claws. ♪
♪ That certain air of savoir faire
in the merry old land of Oz. ♪
♪ Ha... ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha. ♪
♪ Ho, ho, ho. ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha, ♪
♪ Hah! ♪
♫ That's how we laugh
the day away ♫
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♫ That's how we laugh
the day away. ♫
♫ With a ha, ha, ha ♫
♫ Ha, ha, ha. ♫
♫ Ha, ha, ha ♫
♫ in the merry old land of Oz. ♫
♫ Ha, ha, ha. ♫
♫ Ha, ha, ha ♫
oh!
♫ Ha, ha, ha. ♫
Oh!
Who's her? Who's her?
It's the witch! She's
followed us here!
"Surrender Dorothy."
Dorothy? Who's Dorothy?
The Wizard will explain it!
To The Wizard!
Dear, whatever shall we do?
Well, we'd better hurry if we're
going to see The Wizard!
Here! Here, here!
Everything is all right.
Stop that now. Just...
Every...
It's all right!
Everything is all right!
The Great and Powerful Oz has
got matters well in hand.
I hope.
And so you can all go home!
And there's nothing
to worry about!
Get out of here now! Go on.
Go on home and I...
I... go home.
If you please, sir. We want to
see The Wizard right away.
All four of us.
Orders are: Nobody can
see The Great Oz!
Not nobody, not nohow!
Oh, but, but please.
It's very important.
And, and I got a permanent
just for the occasion.
Not nobody! Not nohow!
But she's Dorothy!
The Witch's Dorothy?
Well, that makes a difference.
Just ah...
Wait here. I'll
announce you at once!
Did you hear that? He'll
announce us at once!
I've as good as got my brain!
I can fairly hear
my heart beating.
I'll be home in time for supper!
In another hour, I'll be
king of the forest.
Long live the king!
♪ If I were king of the forest. ♪
♪ Not Queen, not
Duke, not Prince. ♪
♪ My regal robes of the forest. ♪
♪ Would be satin, and not
cotton, and not chintz. ♪
♪ I'd command each thing,
be it fish or fowl. ♪
♪ With a woof and a woof,
and a royal growl. ♪
♪ Woof. ♪
♪ As I click my heel
all the trees would kneel. ♪
♪ And the mountains bow
and the bulls kowtow. ♪
♪ And the sparrow
would a'take wing. ♪
♪ 'F, I...'F, I... were king! ♪
♪ Each rabbit would show
respect a'to me. ♪
♪ The chipmunks
genuflect a'to me. ♪
♪ Though my tail would lash
I would show compash. ♪
♪ For every underling. ♪
♪ 'F, I...'F, I, were king ♪
♪ Just king! ♪
♪ Monarch of all I survey. ♪
♪ Mah, hah, hah, hah, hah, hah,
hah, hah, hah, ha-narch! ♪
♪ Of all I survey! ♪
Your majesty, if you were king you
wouldn't be afraid of anything?
Not nobody! Not nohow!
Not even a rhinoceros?
Imposserous!
How about a hippopotamus?
Why, I'd trash him
from top to bottomamus!
Supposin' you met an elephant?
I'd wrap him up in cellophant!
What if it were a brontosaurus?
I'd show him who was king of the fores'!
How?
How? How?
Courage!
What makes a king
out of a slave?
Courage!
What makes the flag
on the mast to wave?
Courage!
What makes the elephant
charge his tusk
in the misty mist,
or the dusky dusk?
What makes the muskrat
guard his musk?
Courage!
What makes the Sphinx
the Seventh Wonder?
Courage!
What makes the dawn
come up like thunder?
Courage!
What makes the Hottentot so hot?
What puts the "ape" in apricot?
What have they got
that I ain't got?
Courage!
Courage! Courage!
You can say that again.
Hah.
Huh!?
No!
The Wizard says, "Go away!"
Go away? Go away?
Looks like we came
a long way for nothing.
Oh...
And I was so happy!
I thought I was on my way home.
Don't cry, Dorothy!
We're going to get
you to The Wizard.
We certainly are!
Auntie Em was so good to me,
and I never appreciated it.
Running away and
hurting her feelings.
Professor Marvel
said she was sick.
She may be dying
and, and it's all my fault!
Oh, I'll never forgive myself!
Never, never, never!
Please, don't cry anymore.
I'll get you in to
The Wizard somehow.
Come on. I had an
Aunt Em myself once!
Wait a minute, fellahs.
I was just thinkin'.
I really don't want to see
The Wizard this much.
I better wait for you outside.
- What's the matter?
- Oh, he's just a'scared again.
Don't you know The Wizard's going
to give you some courage?
I'd be too scared
to ask him for it.
Oh, well, then,
we'll ask him for you.
I'd sooner wait outside.
But why? Why?
Because I'm still scared!
Ohh!
What happened?
Somebody pulled my tail.
Oh, you did it yourself!
I,... oh...
Come on.
COME FORWARD!
Tell me when it's over!
Oh! Look at that! Look at that!
I want to go home!
I AM OZ
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL!
WHO ARE YOU?
I, if you please, I... I am Dorothy,
the small and meek.
We've come to ask you,...
SILENCE!
Ohhh,
Oh, Jiminy crickets!
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL OZ
KNOWS WHY YOU HAVE COME.
STEP FORWARD, TIN MAN!
Ohhhh!
YOU DARE TO COME TO ME
FOR A HEART, DO YOU?
YOU CLINKING, CLANKING, CLATTERING
COLLECTION OF CALIGINOUS JUNK!
Ohhhh!
Eh, yes... Yes, sir.
Y-Yes, your honor.
You see, a while back
we were walking down The
Yellow Brick Road, and...
QUIET!
Ohhhhhh!
AND YOU, SCARECROW
HAVE THE EFFRONTERY
TO ASK FOR A BRAIN.
YOU BILLOWING BALE
OF BOVINE FODDER!
Yes, your honor. I
mean, your excellency.
I mean, your Wizardry
ENOUGH!
UH, AND YOU, LION!
WELL?
Oh, oh!
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself.
Frightening him like that
when he came to you for help!
SILENCE, WHIPPERSNAPPER!
THE BENEFICENT OZ HAS EVERY INTENTION
OF GRANTING YOUR REQUESTS!
What's that? What'd he say?
Huh? What'd he say?
BUT FIRST, YOU MUST
PROVE YOURSELVES WORTHY
BY PERFORMING A VERY SMALL TASK.
BRING ME THE BROOMSTICK
OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST.
B-b-b-but if we do that, we'll
have to kill her to get it!
BRING ME HER BROOMSTICK
AND I'LL GRANT YOUR REQUESTS.
NOW, GO!
But, but what if she kills us first?
I SAID, "GO!"
"I'd turn back if I were you!"
Grolf.
Grolf!
Grrrolf!
Oh, look! Look! Look!
I believe there're
spooks around here.
That's ridiculous! Spooks!
That's silly.
Don't you believe in spooks?
No. Why only... Oh,
Oh! Oh, Tin Man! Oh!
Oh, are you, are you all right?
I do believe in spooks,
I do believe in spooks.
I do, I do, I do, I do, I do.
I do believe in spooks!
I do!
You'll believe in more than that
before I'm finished with you.
Take your army to The Haunted Forest
and bring me that girl and her dog.
Do what you like with the others, but
I want her alive and unharmed!
They'll give you no trouble.
I promise you that.
I've sent a little insect on ahead
to take the fight out of them.
Take special care of those Ruby Slippers.
I want those most of all.
Now, fly! Fly!
Bring me that girl
and her slippers!
Fly! Fly! Fly!
Help!
Help! Help!
Go away now!
Toto! Toto! Help! Toto!
Aahhh!
Arf! Arf!
Arf!
Aahhh!
Arf! Arf! Arf!
Arf!
Help! Help! Help!
Oh! Well, what happened to you?
They tore my legs off and
threw them over there!
Then they took my chest out
and threw it over there!
Well, that's you all over.
They sure knocked the stuffings
out of you, didn't they?
Don't stand there talking!
Put me together!
We've got to find Dorothy!
Now, let's see,...
What a nice little dog.
And you, my dear, what
an unexpected pleasure.
It's so kind of you to
visit me in my loneliness.
What are you going to do with my dog?
Give him back to me!
All in good time, my little
pretty, all in good time.
Oh, please give me back my dog!
Certainly, certainly,...
when you give me those slippers.
But The Good Witch
of the North told me not to.
Very well.
Throw that basket in the
river and drown him.
No! No. No. Here.
You can have your old slippers
but give me back Toto!
That's a good little girl.
I knew you'd see reason!
Ahhh!
Ah!
I'm sorry. I didn't do it.
Can I still have my dog?
No! Fool that I am, I
should have remembered
those slippers will
never come off
as long as you're alive.
But that's not what's worrying me.
It's how to do it.
These things must
be done delicately
or you hurt the spell.
Run, Toto! Run!
Catch him, you fool!
Ahhh!
Run, Toto, run!
He got away! He got away!
Ohhh! Which is more than you will!
Drat you and your dog!
You've been more trouble to me
than you're worth, one way or another
but it'll soon be over now!
Do you see that? That's how much
longer you've got to be alive!
And it isn't long, my pretty.
It isn't long!
I can't wait forever
to get those shoes!
I'm frightened.
I'm frightened, Auntie
Em, I'm frightened!
Dorothy?
Dorothy, where are you?
It's me, it's Auntie Em.
We're trying to find you!
Where are you?
I'm here in Oz, Auntie Em!
I'm locked up in
the witch's castle
and I'm trying to get
home to you, Auntie Em!
Oh, Auntie Em, don't go away!
I'm frightened!
Come back! Come back!
"Auntie Em. Auntie
Em, come back!"
I'll give you Auntie
Em, my pretty!
Arf!
Arf! Arf!
Look! There's Toto!
Where'd he come from?
Arf! Arf!
Arf!
Why, don't you see? He's
come to take us to Dorothy!
Arf! Arf!
Come on, fellows!
Arf!
Arf! Arf!
Oh! Oh!
I, I, I hope my strength holds out.
I hope your tail holds out.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
What's that? What's that?
That's the castle
of the Wicked Witch!
Dorothy's in that awful place?
Oh, I hate to think of her in there.
We've got to get her out!
Don't cry now. We haven't
got the oil can with us
and you've been squeaking
enough as it is.
Who's them? Who's them?
♫ O-ee-yah! Eoh-ah! ♫
I've got a plan how
to get in there.
Fine. He's got a plan.
And you're going to lead us.
Yeah...
- Me?
- Yes, you.
I...
I, I, gotta get her outta there?
That's right.
All right, I'll go in
there for Dorothy.
Wicked Witch or no Wicked Witch.
Guards or no guards,
I'll tear 'em apart.
Ruff!
I may not come out alive
but I'm going in there.
There's only one thing I
want you fellows to do.
What's that?
Talk me out of it.
No, you don't.
Oh, no!
No? Now, wait a minute.
- Up!
- Now?
Arf!
- Arf!
- Sssh,
Ugh!
Sssh,
♫ O-ee-yah! Eoh-ah! ♫
♫ O-ee-yah! ♫
I've got another idea.
Do you think it'll be polite,
dropping in like this?
Come on.
♫ O-ee-yah! Eoh-ah! ♫
Where do we go now?
Yeah.
Arf! Arf!
Arf!
There!
Arf! Arf!
Arf!
Wait! We'd better make sure.
Dorothy, are you in there?
It's us!
Yes, it's me!
She's locked me in!
Listen, fellows. It's her. We
gotta get her out! Open this door!
Oh, hurry, please hurry!
The hourglass is almost empty!
Stand back!
Oh!
Oh! Toto, Toto!
- Dorothy!
- Lion, darling, I knew you'd come!
I knew you would!
Hurry, we've got
no time to lose!
Going so soon?
I wouldn't hear of it.
Why, my little party's
just beginning.
Trapped! Trapped
like mice, er, rats!
Arf!
That's right. Don't
hurt them right away.
We'll let them think
about it a little, first.
Seize them!
Stop them, you fools!
Stop them! Seize them!
Seize them!
There they go! Ah,
now we've got them!
Half you go this way,
half you go that way!
Hurry! Hurry!
Where do we go now?
This way, come on!
Ohh!
Back! Back!
Well,...
Ring around the rosie! A
pocket full of spears!
Thought you'd be pretty
foxy, didn't you?
Well,...
The last to go will see the
first three go before her!
And her mangy little dog, too!
How about a little
fire, Scarecrow?
No, no, no!
Help! I'm burning! I'm burning!
It's happening! Help!
Don't throw that water!
Ahhhh!
You cursed brat! Look
what you've done!
I'm melting! Melting!
Oh, what a world, what a world!
Who would have thought a good little girl
could destroy my beautiful wickedness?
Ohhh! Look out! Look out!
I'm going.
Ohhh!
ᴼʰʰʰ...
She's.... she's.... dead!
You've killed her!
I didn't mean to kill
her, really I didn't.
It's... it's just that he was on fire!
Hail to Dorothy! The
Wicked Witch is dead!
Hail! Hail to Dorothy! The
The broom!
May we have it?
Please. And take it with you.
Oh, thank you so much!
Now we can go back to The Wizard and
tell him the Wicked Witch is dead!
The Wicked Witch is dead!
CAN I BELIEVE MY EYES?
WHY HAVE YOU COME BACK?
Please, sir. We've
done what you told us.
We've brought you the broomstick
of The Wicked Witch of the West.
We melted her.
OH, YOU LIQUIDATED HER, EH?
VERY RESOURCEFUL!
Yes, sir. So we'd like you to keep your
promise to us, if you please, sir.
NOT SO FAST! NOT SO FAST!
I'LL HAVE TO GIVE THE
MATTER A LITTLE THOUGHT!
GO AWAY, AND COME BACK TOMORROW!
Tomorrow?
Oh, but I want to go home now.
You've had plenty
of time already!
Yeah!
DO NOT AROUSE THE WRATH OF
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL OZ!
I SAID, "COME BACK TOMORROW!"
If you were really great and
powerful, you'd keep your promises!
DO YOU PRESUME TO
CRITICIZE THE GREAT OZ?
YOU UNGRATEFUL CREATURES!
THINK YOURSELVES LUCKY THAT I'M
GIVING YOU AUDIENCE TOMORROW
INSTEAD OF 20 YEARS FROM NOW!
Oh!
THE GREAT OZ HAS SPOKEN!
PAY NO ATTENTION TO THAT
MAN BEHIND THE CURTAIN.
THE GREAT AND... OZ...
HAS SPOKEN!
Who are you?
Oh... I...
I, I AM THE GREAT AND POWERFUL
Wizard of Oz.
You are?
I don't believe you!
No, I'm afraid it's true. There's
no other Wizard except me.
You humbug!
Yeah!
Yes. Yes that's exactly so.
I'm a humbug!
Oh...
You're a very bad man!
Oh, no, my dear, I'm,
I'm a very Goodman.
I'm just a very bad Wizard.
What about the heart that
you promised Tin Man?
And the courage that you
promised Cowardly Lion?
And Scarecrow's brain?
Why, anybody can have a brain.
That's a very mediocre commodity.
Every pusillanimous creature
that crawls on the earth
or slinks through slimy
seas has a brain!
Back where I come from
we have universities
seats of great learning, where
men go to become great thinkers.
And when they come out, they
think deep thoughts
with no more brains
than you have.
But! They have one thing you
haven't got: A diploma!
Therefore, by virtue of the
authority vested in me
by the Universitatus
Committeeatum E Pluribus Unum
I hereby confer upon you
the honorary degree of Th.D.
Th.D.?
Yeah, that...
That's Dr. of Thinkology!
"The sum of the square roots of any
two sides of an isosceles triangle"
"is equal to the square root
of the remaining side."
Oh joy, rapture!
I've got a brain!
How can I ever thank you enough?
Well, you can't.
As for you, my fine friend,
you are a victim of
disorganized thinking.
You're under the
unfortunate delusion
that simply because you run away
from danger you have no courage.
You are confusing
courage with wisdom.
Back where I come from we have
men who are called heroes.
Once a year they take their
fortitude out of mothballs
and parade it down the
main street of the city.
And they have no more
courage than you have.
But they have one thing
that you haven't got:
A medal!
Therefore, for
meritorious conduct
extraordinary valor, conspicuous
bravery against wicked witches
I award you The Triple Cross.
You are now a member of
The Legion Of Courage!
Oh, shucks, folks, I'm speechless!
As for you, my galvanized
friend, you want a heart!
You don't know how lucky
you are not to have one.
Hearts will never be practical until
they can be made unbreakable.
But I still want one.
Back where I come from there are men
who do nothing all day but good deeds.
They are called Phil...
Er, er, Phil, er, yes..
Er, Good-Deed-Doers.
And their hearts are no
bigger than yours.
But they have one thing you
haven't got: A testimonial!
Therefore, in consideration
of your kindness
I take pleasure at this
time in presenting you
with a small token of our
esteem and affection.
And remember, my
sentimental friend
that a heart is not judged
by how much you love
but by how much you
are loved by others.
Ahh...
Oh, it ticks! Listen!
Look, it ticks!
Rea-read what my medal says.
"Courage"!
Ain't it the truth?
Oh, oh, they're all wonderful.
Hey, what about Dorothy?
Yes, how about Dorothy?
Yeah.
Dorothy next!
Yes. Dorothy, ah,
I don't think there's anything
in that black bag for me.
Well, you force me into a
cataclysmic decision.
The only way to get Dorothy back to Kansas
is for me to take her there myself!
Oh, will you? Could you?
Oh!
Oh, but are you a clever
enough Wizard to manage it?
Child, you cut me to the quick!
I'm an old Kansas man myself
born and bred - in the heart
of the western wilderness,
premier balloonist
par excellence
for the Miracle Wonderland
Carnival Company.
Until one day while performing
spectacular feats of stratospheric skill
never before attempted by civilized man,
an unfortunate phenomenon occurred.
The balloon failed to
return to the fair.
It did?
Weren't you frightened?
Frightened? You are talking to a man
who has laughed in the face of death
sneered at doom and
chuckled at catastrophe.
I was petrified.
Then suddenly the wind changed
and the balloon floated down
into the heart of this noble city
where I was instantly acclaimed Oz
the first Wizard deluxe!
Ohhh!
Times being what they
were, I accepted the job
retaining my balloon against
the advent of a quick getaway.
And in that balloon, my dear
Dorothy, you and I will return
to the land of "E Pluribus Unum"!
This is positively the finest
exhibition ever to be shown.
Ah, eh...
Yes, well, be that as it may.
I, your Wizard par ardua ad alta,
am about to embark upon a hazardous
and technically unexplainable journey
into the outer stratosphere!
To confer, converse and otherwise
hobnob with my brother Wizards.
And I hereby decree
that until what time...
(If any...)
that I return, the Scarecrow
by virtue of his highly superior
brains, shall rule in my stead
assisted by the Tin Man, by
virtue of his magnificent heart
and The Lion, by
virtue of his courage!
Obey them as you would me.
Thank you.
Ruff!
Rrow!
Oh, Toto!
Come back! Toto! Toto!
Oh, don't go without me!
I'll be right back! Toto!
Stop that dog!
This is highly irregular procedure!
This is absolutely unprecedented!
Ruined my exit!
Oh!
Come back! Come back!
Don't go without me!
Please, come back!
I can't come back! I
don't know how it works!
Goodbye, folks!
Goodbye!
Bye!
Oh, now I'll never get home!
Stay with us then, Dorothy.
We all love you.
We don't want you to go.
That's very kind of you
but this could never
be like Kansas.
Auntie Em must have stopped wondering
what happened to me by now.
Oh, Scarecrow, what am
I going to do?
Look!
Here's someone who can help you!
Oh, will you help me?
Can you help me?
You don't need to be
helped any longer.
You've always had the power
to go back to Kansas.
I have?
Then why didn't you
tell her before?
Because she wouldn't have believed me.
She had to learn it for herself.
What have you learned, Dorothy?
Well, I,...
I think that it, that it wasn't enough just
to want to see Uncle Henry and Auntie Em.
And it's that if I ever go looking
for my heart's desire again,
I won't look any further
than my own backyard
because if it isn't there
I never really lost
it to begin with.
Is that right?
That's all it is!
But that's so easy! I should
have thought of it for you.
I should have felt it in my heart.
No. She had to find it out for herself.
Now those magic slippers will
take you home in two seconds!
Oh, Toto, too?
Toto, too.
Oh, now?
Whenever you wish.
Oh, dear, that's too
wonderful to be true!
It's going to be so
hard to say goodbye.
I love you all, too.
Goodbye, Tin Man.
Oh, don't cry.
You'll rust so dreadfully.
Here. Here's your oil can.
Goodbye.
Now I know I've got a heart,
'cause it’s breaking.
Goodbye, Lion.
You know, I know it isn't right
but I'm gonna miss the way
you used to holler for help
before you found your courage.
I would never've found it
if it hadn't been for you.
I think I'll miss
you most of all.
Are you ready now?
Yes.
Say goodbye, Toto.
Yes, I'm ready now.
Then close your eyes and tap
your heels together three times.
And think to yourself:
"There's no place like home.
There's no place like home."
There's no place like home.
There's no place...
Wake up, honey.
There's no place like home.
There's no place...
Dorothy! Dorothy, dear.
It's Aunt Em, darling.
Auntie Em, it's you!
Yes darling.
Hello, there! Anybody home?
I, I just dropped by because I heard
the little girl got caught in the big...
Well, she seems all right now!
Yeah, she got quite a bump on the head.
We kinda' thought for a minute
she was gonna' leave us.
But I did leave you, Uncle Henry.
That's just the trouble.
And I tried to get back for days and days.
There, there, lie quiet now.
You just had a bad dream.
Sure.
Remember me, your old pal, Hunk?
And me, Hickory?
You couldn't forget my face, could you?
No. But it wasn't a dream. It was a place.
And you, and you, and you,
and you were there.
But you couldn't have been, could you?
Oh, we dream lots of silly
things when we,...
No, Aunt Em, this was a real,
truly live place.
And I remember that some of it
wasn't very nice
but most of it was beautiful.
But just the same
all I kept saying to everybody
was, "I want to go home!"
And they sent me home.
Doesn't anybody believe me?
Of course we believe you, Dorothy.
But anyway, Toto, we're home!
Home!
And this is my room, and you're all here!
And I'm not going to leave here ever,
ever again, because I love you all!
And, oh, Auntie Em,
there's no place like home!
Sing-along Subtitles By:
MightyMike77020
Kudos to the following wedsite's
for help with these subs:
Http://www.Vidarholen.Net
Dictionary of Interjections
http://www.Writtensound.Com
Onomatopoeia Dictionary
http://www.Rapidtables.Com
Web Colors-RGB Color Codes Chart
If you would like to comment
on my Read-along, Sing-along subtitles,
would like to suggest a movie to subtitle, I'm
at http://subscene.com/u/759958/subtitles